<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Job on John, Complected</title>
    <link>https://john-nicholson.github.io/tags/new-job/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New Job on John, Complected</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 21:33:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://john-nicholson.github.io/tags/new-job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I love it when a plan comes together</title>
      <link>https://john-nicholson.github.io/posts/ecg-when-a-plan-comes-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 21:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://john-nicholson.github.io/posts/ecg-when-a-plan-comes-together/</guid>
      <description>So I thought these posts would happen more regularly; it&amp;rsquo;s just been intense getting to know so many people. Bringing together three teams distributed across our campuses has been a great deal of fun. Each is unique, with its distinct strengths and culture. Today I shared our strategy for IT across the group. While I get nervous speaking in front of people, I love these moments. It&amp;rsquo;s the big reveal of the analysis and work that has been amassed over the last 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Incident and an Attack</title>
      <link>https://john-nicholson.github.io/posts/ecg-an-incident-and-an-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://john-nicholson.github.io/posts/ecg-an-incident-and-an-attack/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a mad week at one of the sites, we experienced a cyber attack and the fact it&amp;rsquo;s been in the first couple of months</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Entertaining Start</title>
      <link>https://john-nicholson.github.io/posts/ecg-an-entertaining-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://john-nicholson.github.io/posts/ecg-an-entertaining-start/</guid>
      <description>So at the beginning of the month I began a new adventure as an employee for the first time in 7 years, starting as the new Group Director for IT with Eastern Colleges Group. I really am excited about this role, there is so much to get to grips with, so many areas in which IT directly contributes to the eduction delivered by the colleges. I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting sporadically (if I ever get this blog published) with how the role is going and the challeges that we face in ensuring that the systems keep working.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
